Finding Aid for the Paul D. Boyer Papers, 1943-2009 LSC.2156
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Academia, 1941-2008; 1960-1993
  - Subseries 1.2: Publications, 1949-2007; 1970-2002
    - Articles: Hiller and Carmeli, "Kinetic analysis of cooperative interactions induced by Mn2+ binding..."., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Articles: Hutton and Boyer, "Subunit Interaction during Catalysis"., 1979 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Articles: Inesi, Lewis, and Murphy, "Interdependence of H +, Ca 2+, and P i (or vanadate) sites in sarcoplasmic reticulum ATPase"., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Articles: Janson, Degani, and Boyer, "The Formation of Enzyme-bound and Equilibrium Pyrophosphate and the Molecular Basis of the Oxygen Exchange Reaction..."., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Articles: Kandal, Melese, Stroop, and Boyer, "Mitochondrial F1-ATPase will Bind and Cleave ATP..."., 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Articles: Kasho and Boyer, "ITP and HCO 3- Modulations of Oxygen Exchange by F1 ATPase"., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Articles: Kasho and Boyer, "Relationships of ITP and HCO 3- on F1 ATPase..."., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Articles: Kasho, Yoshida, and Boyer, "F1 ATPase from PS3 (TF1) shows ATP Modulation..."., 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Articles: Kasho and Baykov, "Two pathways for phosphate/water oxygen exchange"., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Articles: Kasho and Boyer, "Vacuolar ATPases"., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Articles: Kasho and Boyer, "Vacuolar ATPases, like F1-F0 ATPases, show a strong dependence of the reaction velocity..."., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Articles: Kasho, Allison, and Boyer, "Study of the mechanism of the MF1 ATPase inhibition..."., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Articles: Kayalar, Rosing, and Boyer, "An Alternating Site Sequence for Oxidative Phosphorylation Suggested by Measurement of Substrate Binding Patterns and Exchange Reaction Inhibitions"., 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Articles: Kohlbrenner and Boyer, "Catalytic Properties of Beef Heart Mitochondrial ATPase Modified with..."., 1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Articles: Kohlbrenner and Boyer, "Characteristics of the Residual ATPase Activity of NBF-Modified F1 from Mitochondria"., 1981 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Articles: Kolhbrenner and Boyer, "Probes of Catalytic Site Cooperativity"., 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Articles: Kohlbrenner and Boyer, "One type of catalytic site will account for mitochondrial synthesis and hydrolysis of ATP"., 1980 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Articles: Marlene O., "A Brief Account of the Purported Discovery of Phosphohistidine" (joke manuscript)., 1963 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Articles: McIntosh and Boyer, "ATP Modulation of Catalytic Intermediates of Ca 2+"., 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Articles: McIntosh and Boyer, "Correlations between Catalytic Activity of Ca 2+-ATPase of Sarcoplasmic Reticulum and Alterations in Membrane Integrity..."., 1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Articles: McIntosh and Boyer, "Interactions of a Nonionic Detergent with Sarcoplasmic Reticulum..."., 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Articles: Melese and Boyer, "CF 2 and F1 ATPase Subunit Heterogeneity and their Modulation by Catalysis"., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Articles: Melese and Boyer, "Heterogeneity in the isoelectric profile of chloroplast..."., 1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Articles: Melese and Boyer, "Derivation of the Catalytic Subunits of the Chloroplast ATPase..."., 1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Articles: Melese, Xue, and Boyer, "Catalytic Properties of Chloroplast F1-ATPase Modified...by 2-Azido Adenine Nucleotides"., circa 1988 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Articles: Milgrom and Boyer, "The ADP that binds tightly to...F1-ATPase..."., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Articles: Milgrom, Ehler, and Boyer, "ATP Binding at Noncatalytic Sites..."., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Articles: Milgrom, Ehler, and Boyer, "Noncatalytic sites of chloroplast F1-ATPase" (1 of 2)., 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Articles: Milgrom, Ehler, and Boyer, "Noncatalytic sites of chloroplast F1-ATPase" (2 of 2)., 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Articles: Milgrom "When beef-heart mitochondrial F1-ATPase is inhibited..."., 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Articles: Milgrom, Murataliev, and Boyer, "Bi-site activation occurs with native and nucleotide-depleted mitochondrial F1-ATPase"., 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Articles: Mitchell, Peter; misc. titles, 1960s (1 of 2). (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Articles: Mitchell, Peter; misc. titles, 1960s (2 of 2). (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Articles: Mitchell, Peter; misc. titles 1970s. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Articles: Mitchell, Peter; misc. titles, 1980s (1 to 2). (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Articles: Mitchell, Peter; misc. titles, 1980s (2 of 2). (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Articles: Morales, Horowitz, and Bolts, "The Distribution of Tracer Substrate in an Enzyme-Substrate System"., 1962 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Articles: Murataliev, Milgrom, and Boyer, "Characteristics of the Combination of Inhibitory Mg 2+ and Azide..."., 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Articles: Murataliev, "Adenine nucleotide binding at a noncatalytic site..."., 1992 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Articles: Murataliev and Boyer, "The Mechanism of Stimulation of MgATPase..."., 1992 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Articles: Murataliev and Boyer, "Interaction of Mitochondrial F1-ATPase with trinitrophenyl derivatives of ATP and ADP" (1 of 2)., 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Articles: Murataliev and Boyer, "Interaction of Mitochondrial F1-ATPase..." (2 of 2)., 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Articles: Myers and Boyer, "Oxygen and Deuterium Exchanges Show Reversal of the Catalytic Steps of Citrate synthase"., 1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Articles: O'Neal and Boyer, "Assessment of the Rate of Bound Substrate"., 1983 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Articles: O'Neal, Bild, Smith, and Boyer, "The Facile Oxygen Exchanges of Phosphoenolpyruvate and Preparation of 18 O Phosphoenolpyruvate"., 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Articles: Rosen, Gresser, Vinkler, and Boyer, "Assessment of Total Catalytic Sites and the Nature of Bound Nucleotide Participation in Photophosphorylation"., 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Articles: Rosing, Kayalar, and Boyer, "Evid. for Energy Dep. Change in Phosphate Binding"., 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Articles: Segal, Kachmar, and Boyer, "Kinetic Analysis of Enzyme Reactions"., 1949-1952 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Articles: Sleep, Hackney, and Boyer, "Characterization of Phophate Oxygen Exchange Reactions Catalyzed by Myosin..."., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Articles: Sleep and Hutton, "Exchange Between Inorganic Phosphate and adenosine 5' triphosphate in the Medium by Actomyosin subfragment 1"., 1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Articles: Sleep and Homsher, unpublished article on myofibrils 18 O., 1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Articles: Sleep, Hackney, and Boyer, "The Equivalence of Phosphate Oxygens for Exchange and the Hydrolysis characteristics Revealed by the Distribution of 18 O-Pi species"., 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Articles: Smith and Boyer, "Properties of ATP Tightly Bound to Catalytic Sites of Chloroplast ATP Synthase"., 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Articles: Strayer and Boyer, "Integrity of Parental DNA during Replication"., 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Articles: Stroop and Boyer, "Chloroplast ATP synthase as Revealed by Reaction at Low ADP"., 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Articles: unknown, "An outline of elementary statistical methods"., undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Articles: Vinkler, Avron, and Boyer, "The Initial Formation of ATP in Photophosphorylation Does Not Require a Proton Gradient"., 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Articles: Vinkler, Rosen, and Boyer, "Light-driven ATP Formation from 32 P i..."., 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Articles: Vinkler, Avron, and Boyer, "Effects of Permanent Buffers on the Initial Time Course of Photophosphorylation and Postillumination Phosphorylation"., 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Articles: Wannlund, DeLuca, Stempel, and Boyer, "Use of 16 C-Carboxyl-Luciferin in Determining the Mechanism of the Firefly Luciferase Catalyzed Reactions"., 1978 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Articles: Wise, unknow title, regarding mutant ATPases., 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Articles: Xue, Melese, Stempel, Reedy, and Boyer, "Properties of Chloroplast F1-ATPase Partially Modified by 2-Azido Adenine Nucleotides..."., 1988 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Articles: Xue and Boyer, "Modulation of GTPase activity by ATP binding at noncatalytic sites..."., 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Articles: Zhou and Boyer, "MgADP and Free P i as the substrates..."., 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Articles: Zhou and Boyer, "Evidence that energization of the chloroplast ATP synthase..." (1 of 2)., 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Articles: Zhou and Boyer, "Evidence that energization of the chloroplast ATP synthase..." (2 of 2). +1 Floppy disc., 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Floppy disc labeled "Backup #13 Disckcopy of the T.M. disk" with the phrase "Backup #13" striked-out.
    - Articles: misc. authors, 1950s and 1970s., 1956, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      Contains copy of Swanson's article "Studies on the non-oxidative exchange between the inorganic phosphate and ATP, as catalyzed by intact mitochondria" (1956), Hinkle and McCarty's "How Cells Make ATP" in Scientific American (1978), and Wimmer and Rose's "Mechanism for Oxygen Exchange in the Chloroplast Photophosphorylation System" (1977).
    - Articles: misc. authors, assorted titles (1 of 2)., 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Articles: misc. authors, assorted titles (2 of 2)., 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Articles: misc. authors, assorted titles (1 of 2)., 1990-2004 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Articles: misc. authors, assorted titles (2 of 2)., 1990-2004 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Articles: misc. figures and slides (1 of 2)., undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Articles: misc. figures and slides (2 of 2)., undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Articles: misc. negatives of figures., 1990s (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Articles: misc. possible figures., undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Book Chapters: Boyer and Stempel, "Rapid Nucleotide Labeling and 18 O Exchange Rates of Intermediate States in Electron Transport-coupled Phosphorylation" for Methods in Enzymology., 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Book Chapters: Boyer, Hackney, Vinkler, Gresser, Choate, "Nucleotide Binding and ATPase Subunit Cooperativity in Energy-Transduction by Mitochondria and Chloroplasts" for Structure and Function of Energy Transducing Membranes., 1978 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Book Chapters: Boyer, "Some Approaches to the Understanding of Oxidative Phosphorylation" in Of Oxygen, Fuels, and Living Matter., 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Book Chapters: Boyer, "The Coupling of Proton Translocation to ATP Formation" for Mitochondria and Microsomes: In Honor of Professor Lars Ernster., 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Book Chapters: Boyer, "H+-ATP synthetases - possible stages in the reaction sequence" for The Proton Cycle: In Honor of Peter Mitchell., 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Book Chapters: Boyer, "Enzymology" for the Academic Press Dictionary of Science and Technology., 1990 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Book Chapters: Boyer and Kohlbrenner, "The present status of the Binding-Change Mechanism and its Relation to ATP Formation by Chloroplasts" for Energy Coupling in Photosynthesis., 1981 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Book Chapters: Hackney, Stempel, and Boyer, "Oxygen-18 Probes of Enzymatic Reactions of Phosphate Compounds" for Methods in Enzymology., 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Book Chapters: Stempel and Boyer, "Refinements in 18 O Methodology" for Methods in Enzymology., 1985 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 1.3: Conferences, 1967-2005; 1970-2002
    Contains materials related to the numerous meetings and lectures that Paul Boyer attended from the 1960s to the 1990s. Most of the records pertain to research symposiums held by universities in the US as well as countries abroad such as Italy, Israel, South Africa, the Netherlands, and Thailand, to name a few. Conferences held by scientific societies such as the American Chemical Society (ACS), the American Society of Biological Chemists (ASBC, later the American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology or ASBMB), the European Bioenergetics Conference (EBEC), and the Federation of European Biochemical Societies (FEBS) comprise the rest of the materials. Professor Boyer cites the Gordon Research Conferences (GRC) as having been particularly meaningful to him throughout his career. The GRC folders often contain group photos of conference attendees, comprising the majority of the collection's sparse photographic content. Some folders contain minimal information such as plane tickets and confirmation of attendance, although others have notes that Boyer took at those conferences as well as related correspondence.
    Items are positioned (with a few exceptions) within boxes chronologically by the date of the conference and then alphabetically by conference title or venue.
    - Conferences: Australian Biochemical Society, "Some Approaches to the Understanding of Oxidative and Photosynthetic Phosphorylation" lecture, 1967., 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Conferences: State University of New York at Buffalo seminars, 1967., 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Conferences: GRC July 29-August 2, 1968 "Energy Coupling Mechanisms". (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Conferences: National Academy of Sciences, Autumn 1968 meeting. (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Conferences: Notre Dame Nieuwland and Reilly lectureships, 1968., 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Conferences: Oak Ridge National Laboratory Distinguished Lecture, 1968. (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Conferences: Princeton University seminar, "Some Isotopic Probes of Enzyme Mechanisms", 1969., 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Conferences: U of Alberta seminar, 1969., 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Conferences: U of Bari Aldo Moro Round Table Discussion on Electron Transport and Energy Conservation, 1969., 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Conferences: U of Illinois, the Drickamer Committee on the Future of Biochemistry, 1969. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Conferences: U of Southern California seminar, 1969. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Conferences: U of Utah seminar, 1969., 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Conferences: Cal State College Fullerton seminar, 1970. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Conferences: Cal State College Long Beach seminar, 1970. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Conferences: Colloquium on Bioenergetics, "Energy linkage to transport and phosphorylation in mitochondrial, bacterial, and microsomal membranes", 1970., 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Conferences: Columbia University Pathobiology Conference, "Energy of Transport and Phosphorylation by Membrane Structure" lecture., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Conferences: Cornell University seminar, 1970. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Conferences: 2nd Enzyme Mechanism Conference, "Enolase Mechanism" lecture., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Conferences: GRC June 29-July 3, 1970 "Enzymes, Coenzymes, and Metabolic Pathways". (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Conferences: 8th International Conference on Biochemistry, "The mode of energy coupling to active transport of amino acids and sugars by E. Coli"., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Conferences: ACS Symposium., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Conferences: Cal State College LA seminar, 1971. (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Conferences: Enzyme Reaction Mechanisms Symposium., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Conferences: GRC August 30-September 3, 1971 "Energy Coupling Mechanisms". (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Conferences: International Symposium on the Biochemistry and Biophysics of Mitochondrial Membranes., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Conferences: Intrascience Research Conference on Mechanisms of Enzyme Action., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Conferences: University of Arizona seminar, 1971. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Conferences: UC Irvine seminar, 1971. (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Conferences: UC San Diego seminar, 1971. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Conferences: Cal State College Long Beach seminar, 1972., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Conferences: 3rd Enzyme Mechanism Conference, 1972., 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Conferences: GRC July 3-7, 1972 "Enzymes, Coenzymes and Metabolic Pathways"., 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Conferences: Loma Linda University, Sigma Xi seminar 1972. (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Conferences: Penn State Biochemistry-Biophysics-Chemistry-Microbiology Interscience Seminar, 1972. (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Conferences: St. Louis University Wendell H. Griffith Memorial Lecture, 1972., 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Conferences: U Michigan seminar, 1972., 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Conferences: U Minnesota seminar, 1972., 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Conferences: U of Texas seminar, 1972., 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Conferences: The Biochemical Society meeting, 1973., 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Conferences: CSU Fullerton seminar, 1973. (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Conferences: Energy-Transducing Membrane Functions Symposium in honor of Britton Chance "Coformational Coupling in Biological Energy Transductions" lecture., 1973 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Conferences: 9th International Congress of Biochemistry, "Catalysts and Mechanism of ATP Synthesis" lecture., 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Conferences: International Symposium on Membrane Proteins in Transport and Phosphorylation., 1973 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Conferences: Tel Aviv University Decennial Symposium, 1973. (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Conferences: UC Riverside seminar, 1973. (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Conferences: University of Hawaii Special Topics in Biochemistry and Biophysics Colloquia, 1973., 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Conferences: ACS Orange County Section seminar, 1974. (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Conferences: ASBC Biophysical Society, 1974. (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Conferences: Caltech seminar, 1974. (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Conferences: GRC July 8-12, 1974: "Energy Coupling Mechanisms"., 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Conferences: Squaw Valley conference, 1974., 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Conferences: UC All-University conference, 1974. (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Conferences: UC San Francisco seminar, 1974. (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Conferences: U of Missouri "Energy Transduction in Mitochondria, Muscle, and Membranes", 1974., 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Conferences: GRC June 30-July 4, 1975 "Muscle: Contraction Mechanism"., 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Conferences: International Symposium on the Structural Basis of Membrane Function, "Bound Nucleotides and Conformational Coupling in Mitochondrial and Chloroplast Phosphorylations" lecture., 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Conferences: Pacific Slope Biochemical Conference., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Conferences: Pontifical Academy of Sciences Conference on Membranes in Biological Transport., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Conferences: Squaw Valley Conference, 1975., 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Conferences: University of Bari Aldo Moro International Symposium on Electron Transfer Chains and Ox Phos., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Conferences: UC San Diego seminar, 1975. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Conferences: U of Florida seminar, 1975., 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Conferences: 4th Aharon Katzir-Katchalsky Conference on Coupling Reactions in Biological Systems, "The Present Status of Conformational Coupling Hypothesis" lecture., 1976 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Conferences: Brandeis U seminar, 1976., 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Conferences: GRC June 14-18, 1976 "Enzymes, Coenzymes, and Metabolic Pathways". (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Conferences: 10th International Congress of Biochemistry, 1976., 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Conferences: Purdue U seminar, 1976. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Conferences: Scripps Institute seminar, 1976. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Conferences: Syracuse & Rensselaer U seminar, 1976. (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Conferences: UC Berkeley Seminar, 1976. (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Conferences: UC Santa Barbara seminar, 1976. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Conferences: U of Iowa seminar, 1976. (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Conferences: U of Kansas seminar, 1976., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Conferences: U of Pennsylvania seminar, 1976. (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Conferences: U of Southern California Pharmacology seminar, 1976. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Conferences: U of Texas Faculty seminar, 1976. (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Conferences: ASBC meeting, April 1977. (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Conferences: Arizona State U seminar, 1977. (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Conferences: Cal State Northridge seminar, 1977. (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Conferences: Colorado State U seminar, 1977. (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Conferences: Columbia U seminar, 1977., 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Conferences: 5th Enzyme Mechanisms Conference, "Relations of Binding, Catalysis, and Conformation Accompanying ATP and Pyrophosphate Hydrolysis" lecture, 1977., 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Conferences: GRC June 26-July 1, 1977 "Energy Coupling Mechanisms"., 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Conferences: ICN-UCLA Symposium on Molecular and Cellular Biology, "Cross-linking of inner mitochondrial membrane components" presentation., 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 29)
      General
      ICN - International Chemical and Nuclear Corporation
    - Conferences: International Symposium on "Mechanisms of Proton and Calcium Pumps", "Relations of Protein Conformation to Enzyme Catalysis and to Proton and Calcium Transport" lecture., 1977 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Conferences: Ohio Statue U seminar, 1977., 1976 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Conferences: Royal Netherlands Academy of Arts and Sciences workshop "Structure and Function of Energy-transducing membranes" in honor of EC Slater., 1977 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Conferences: UC Davis Seminar Program in Biochemistry, Cellular, and Molecular Biology, 1977. (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Conferences: U of Padova International Symposium on Mechanisms of Proton and Calcium Pumps, "Evidence for cooperative catalysis by alternating sites in sarcoplasmic reticulum ATPase and related enzymes" lecture., 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Conferences: U of Virginia seminar, 1977. (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Conferences: 3rd US-USSR Symposium on Myocardial Metabolism, "New insights into ATP synthesis by heart mitochondria" lecture., 1976 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Conferences: ASBC conference abstracts, 1978., 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Conferences: ASBC meeting, June 1978. (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Conferences: American Society for Microbiology Annual Meeting, 1978., 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Conferences: 12th FEBS Meeting, "Energy Linked Conformational Coupling in ATP synthesis" presentation., 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Conferences: Hungarian Academy of Sciences Biochemical Committee's "New Trends in the Description of the General Mechanism and Regulation of Enzymes", "18 O Exchange and Rapid Mixing Probes of Ox. Phos." lecture., 1978 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Conferences: Michigan State U seminar, 1978., 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Conferences: Northwestern U seminar, 1978. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Conferences: UC Santa Cruz Chemistry Colloquium, 1978. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Conferences: U of Minnesota seminar, 1978., 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Conferences: U Penn "Frontiers of Biological Energetics: Electrons to Tissues" Symposium in honor of Britton Chance, "Coupling of Redox and Electrochemical Gradients to ATP" lecture., 1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)